sharedreviews.com 2013-05-07

# Sharedreviews Privacy Policy

  *   * Privacy Policy

Sharedreviews Inc. ("Sharedreviews", "us" or "we") recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others ("Users") who use this site (the " Site") value their privacy. This policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of Personal Information collected on the Site. Sharedreviews provides this policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Site. For the purposes of this policy, "Personal Information" means any information about you except your business title, address, e-mail address, telephone number or facsimile number. It also does not include your home address and telephone number if these are published in a telephone or other directory, and does not include any Review, content or other materials that you post or submit to use for possible publication. Capitalized terms not otherwise defined herein have the meaning set forth in the terms of use. 

1\. Accountability.

We are responsible for the Personal Information under our control and we have designated the Chief Executive Officer as being responsible for our compliance with this policy and with privacy legislation. If you wish to contact the Chief Executive Officer, you can do so by sending an e-mail to: privacy@sharedreviews.com. 

2\. Collection.

When you use the Site, we may collect the following information: (a) registration information: information such as your name and email address when you choose to register to Participate; (b) information to facilitate revenue sharing with you, such as Paypal or other payment processing account information; and (c) usage information, such as the use of cookies to identify you when you use the site, logfile information, including your IP address, browser type, clicks, and time and date of use, all of which may be associated with your identity. 

3\. Use.

Your Personal Information is used or disclosed by us only for the purposes identified in this policy and access to your personal information is limited to our employees and third parties who need to have access to it for the specified purposes. Your Personal Information may used by us to: (a) operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Site; (b) facilitate your Participation and the sharing of revenue with you; (c) identify you and your Reviews to third parties and to other users of the Site; (d) advise you of new features or Services of the Site or otherwise offered by us or by our business partners; (e) facilitate ease of use for the site, such as remembering your information to avoid the need to re-enter it on your next visit, or to provide customized content or information; and (f) monitor the effectiveness and usefulness of our site. You may also disclose Personal Information through the use of the Site, such as by including your Personal Information in messages or comments that are publicly displayed. You can choose what Personal Information you disclose, or whether to disclose anything at all. We also reserve the right, upon an actual or proposed asset sale, merger, acquisition, sale, change of control, or similar transaction, to disclose, transfer or assign Personal Information we have collected from our Users as part of such transaction or in the course of disclosures reasonably required to investigate the possibility of such a transaction. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our third party business partners and service providers for the purposes set forth above. We may also disclose your Personal Information where we are required or permitted by law to do so. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used. 

4\. Retention.

We retain your Personal Information only as long as we require it to provide you access to the Site and to maintain an appropriate historical record of our relationship with you. If there are legal requirements relating to the period of time which we must retain your Personal Information, we comply with those requirements. 

5\. Your Choices.

Most of the Personal Information which we collect, use and disclose is necessary for the purposes described above. If you do not want us to use or disclose your personal information in a particular way, please contact the Chief Executive Officer as described above and we will be pleased to discuss with you how we can limit collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. Note, however, that any limitation may impact on your ability to use the Site, the Services and may impact on your ability to Participate. You have a right to access the Personal Information which we have about you and to request that personal information which you believe to be inaccurate be corrected. If you wish to access your Personal Information, or you have questions or concerns about this policy or about the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information, you should contact the Chief Executive Officer. 

6\. Changes.

This policy may be revised periodically. Any such changes will be posted to the Site and will be effective as of the date noted in the policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to any future revisions. For revisions to this policy that may be materially less restrictive on our collection, use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

**Version 1.00. Last Updated: May 14, 2007**
